







Business Analyst seeking roles in Product Management



Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: MBA/PGDM [Hospital and Healthcare

Notice Period: 2 Months

Management]

Current Designation: Business Analyst

Current Company: Lumedx Healthcare Technologies

Current Location: Mumbai

Pref. Location: Hyderabad, Mumbai, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Business Analyst

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Sr. Implementation Consultant, Business Analyst, Hospital Management Information System, Business Analysis, Software Implementation, Functional Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Clinical Documentation, Regression

Testing, Integration Testing, JIRA, Agile Verified : Le Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

# Summary

Medical Graduate (Physiotherapist), Post Graduate in Hospital & Healthcare Management with 9.6 years of work-experience (6 years as a Consultant & 3.6 years of Clinical Experience)

Executed various projects for Hospitals & Medical Centre from Planning of Hospitals to Implementation of NABH Standards & HMIS (Hospital Management Information System) Solutions, with predefined timelines on an individual/team basis & utmost coordination.

#### **Work Experience**

- Lumedx Healthcare Technologies as Business Analyst Sep 2020 to Till Date
- Allscripts as Sr. Implementation Consultant -IT Jul 2017 to Mar 2020

Projects: Mount Alvernia Hospital (Singapore), Gippsland Health Alliance (Australia), CIMA Hospital (Costa Rica), Dudley Group NHS Foundation Trust (UK), Wise Health System (Texas), Wycoff Heights Medical Centre (Brooklyn), Summit Healthcare (Arizona), Blueprint Clinical Content Building for UK Hospitals.

#### **Key Responsibilities**

Interacting with client users, understanding and documenting the requirements and workflows.

Defining the build requirements as per the workflow and requirements.

Defining the coding standards in the clinical document elements.

Implemented Core Measures related to MIPS, helping organizations to be compliant with MACRA measures.

Designing UI for clinical documents with focus on ease of charting the documents for clinicians.

Configuring and building clinical content defining the integration points and workflow

Handling team in peer reviewing, QA checks and Data Mgrations.

Preparation of Test Cases and Test Data. Performing Unit, Regression and Integration testing for all builds.

Co-ordinate with Onshore and Offshore activities related to work distribution

Responsible for mentoring the team and meeting the timelines related to EMR build.

Providing detailed analysis, build and testing instructions to every build that needs to move to production.

Resolving the analyst's queries related to build specifications and testing of the functionality. Providing L1 and onsite Support for Hospitals during GO LIVE.

Century Informatics as Functional Consultant (HMIS) Jun 2015 to Jun 2017

Projects: Medical Centre, 100 Bedded Multi-Specialty Hospital, 350 Bedded Super-Specialty Hospital, Medical Centre-Middle East & 250 Bedded Multi-Specialty Hospital.

Modules: Revenue Cycle Management, EMR, RIS, PACS, LIS, Inventory Management, Pharmacy, Clinical & Ancillary

Modules (Dietary, CSSD, Linen & Laundry)

## **Important**

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

**Key Responsibilities** 

Interacting with Key Stake-Holders of client organization, understanding the overall Business Model, Key Processes, Specific Pain Areas and Concerns related to Business Processes

Specific Pain Areas and Concerns related to Business Processes.

Analyzing & deciding appropriate processes/systems to meet operational/business requirements of clients.

Interacting with the Management and Key Users from customer's end to understand the present status of processes

and note the critical points for improvement/trouble shooting or to provide context for customization. Solution Mapping Documentation Completion by understanding the processes of the Client's organization and finalizing the same with agreement with the client.

Explaining the Technical team on the finalized processes and identifying the areas for configuration and development for better understanding of the completion of the project.

Internal Testing of application by creating Test Boards and Scenarios, Identifying Issues and Maintaining Logs for the same.

Onsite Implementation of the Application by giving product walkthroughs/demonstrations to Client Organization Key Users for individual modules & finalizing on the Functionality Acceptance Training.

Trial run, giving the end users complete orientation of the system processes and scenarios and documenting the same.

Data mapping for integration of financial modules with Mcrosoft Dynamics, assisting technical team with HL7 integration with PACS. Assisting technical team with identifying and troubleshooting interface issues. Identifying and troubleshooting basic issues through SQL.

GO LIVE support, post successful Trial run and user understanding of processes within the system. Keeping abreast with the trends and common process related pain points in the healthcare industries to provide improvement-oriented inputs to product road map teams.

#### AHA (Academy of Hospital Administration) as Freelance Consultant Apr 2015 to May 2015

Worked with AHA on "Hand Book for Planning & Organizing Hospital Services (Clinical & Supportive Services) - A Guide for Health Systems Planners & Hospital Operations Managers" in collaboration with NHSRC (National Health Systems Resource Centre).

Preparation of guide giving description about the location of the services in the facility, layout of the department, staffing requirements, space requirements, policies, procedures and operational management of the services. Detailed description of HMS (Hospital Management Information System) for a hospital, giving in depth view of the HMS System Requirements, Network Management including System Management, Server Management, Security & Management, aspects involved in Information Security. Brief description on the core modules in HMS and their interplay with each other.

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

UG: Bachelor (Physical Therapy) from rajiv gandhi university of health sciences, bangalore in 2007

PG: MBA/PGDM (Hospital and Healthcare Management) from Institute of Health Management and Research in 2013

^ Back to Top

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
JIRA			

^ Back to Top

### Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Marathi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

## **Affirmative Action**

## **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.